<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AppAndroidTP</string>
    <string name="article_1">Tiramisu jujubes gummies macaroon sweet roll icing apple pie sesame snaps I love. Donut halvah biscuit halvah toffee I love halvah. Lollipop halvah pudding pastry donut shortbread pastry candy. Brownie chupa chups tootsie roll danish chocolate bar croissant bonbon topping tootsie roll. Jujubes gummies jelly dessert chocolate bar lemon drops jelly beans candy canes I love. Ice cream cookie chupa chups I love lollipop donut. Candy canes lollipop halvah tart halvah donut liquorice I love bonbon. Oat cake pastry croissant marzipan shortbread icing. Donut jelly I love carrot cake fruitcake jujubes. Soufflé tiramisu I love I love cookie. Pudding cupcake toffee halvah cheesecake fruitcake I love. Marzipan cotton candy gummi bears powder bear claw danish I love dessert tiramisu. Marzipan bonbon caramels chocolate bear claw. Soufflé cheesecake sweet roll sweet roll pudding.
        \n \n
Chocolate carrot cake dragée apple pie sugar plum I love tiramisu. Soufflé gingerbread I love chocolate pastry. Pudding shortbread pastry cake jujubes cake marzipan jelly beans. Gingerbread I love danish donut gummi bears I love brownie. Macaroon brownie icing danish wafer brownie jelly beans. Muffin cake gummi bears jujubes donut I love jelly-o. Soufflé cheesecake gummi bears jelly tiramisu. Powder chocolate cake jujubes dragée halvah jelly beans dessert I love dragée. Gummi bears chocolate bar I love icing chocolate chupa chups. Marzipan tart jujubes gingerbread cake. Pie caramels icing danish fruitcake dragée cookie shortbread. Chupa chups icing pastry lollipop I love cheesecake danish. Soufflé wafer pie halvah chocolate bar lemon drops.
\n \n
Macaroon jujubes candy canes croissant caramels. Dragée bonbon powder ice cream fruitcake candy canes chocolate I love candy. Chupa chups biscuit apple pie tootsie roll tiramisu I love tootsie roll ice cream bear claw. Chocolate cake caramels cookie topping liquorice chupa chups croissant macaroon I love. Tart topping cake toffee bonbon. Apple pie cupcake oat cake muffin biscuit I love soufflé chocolate bar jelly-o. Macaroon dragée macaroon sweet roll powder gummi bears. Fruitcake apple pie brownie ice cream gummies. Bonbon chupa chups sesame snaps icing lemon drops. Jujubes candy pudding sweet caramels jujubes soufflé lemon drops. Tart chocolate bar oat cake cotton candy marzipan. Muffin I love jujubes marshmallow icing I love I love. Liquorice carrot cake lollipop cupcake powder.
\n \n
Tart bear claw gummi bears liquorice I love. I love chupa chups cotton candy chocolate I love marshmallow I love. Jelly beans toffee candy canes bonbon macaroon chocolate cake gummies topping I love. Cake macaroon I love gingerbread chocolate I love bonbon cheesecake marshmallow. Cupcake cupcake tiramisu shortbread tart marshmallow pudding. Ice cream lemon drops jujubes fruitcake jujubes I love caramels. Cookie chocolate donut chupa chups I love biscuit. Chupa chups lemon drops cake oat cake oat cake candy sugar plum pudding. Dragée pie jelly chupa chups powder jelly gummies shortbread. Gummies I love I love bonbon I love donut cookie bear claw gummies. Candy canes caramels gummi bears pastry cake gingerbread. Cupcake chocolate bar cheesecake wafer sugar plum jujubes I love muffin.
\n \n
Carrot cake marzipan apple pie powder soufflé donut. Halvah topping candy canes sesame snaps apple pie gingerbread. Sesame snaps sesame snaps marzipan candy apple pie I love. Dragée cupcake chocolate apple pie biscuit apple pie bear claw cake. Topping chocolate chupa chups sugar plum candy canes cake fruitcake. Candy canes topping lollipop pie lollipop. Halvah bonbon tiramisu I love chupa chups pudding. Croissant jelly dragée cake I love halvah marshmallow cotton candy. Croissant bear claw apple pie wafer jujubes ice cream fruitcake toffee. Jelly beans chocolate cake I love croissant gummies. Chocolate bar chocolate cake cotton candy jelly beans I love gingerbread I love marzipan apple pie. I love cake cake gingerbread pudding soufflé candy canes.</string>

    <string name="lancer_page_saisie">Lancer la page de saisie</string>
    <string name="submit_button">Valider</string>
    <string name="libelle_memo">MEMO</string>
    <string name="default_text">Hello</string>
    <string name="legende_favori">Vous avez appuié sur l\'étoile</string>
</resources>